<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Garrison Real Estate Video Blog</title>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Ben Garrison - your professional New Jersney Real Estate Agent.</description>
    <link>localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 11:56:27 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 11:56:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Maplewood/South Orange Market Update</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/satbIWON7lk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever people ask me how the current real estate market is, I tell them that the straight-board answer really depends on which town you live in or which town you’re looking to buy in. That being said, &lt;strong&gt;all the New Jersey towns with direct train access to New York City generally are in a really strong market right now. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Maplewood, sales are currently running about 10% ahead of where they were this time last year. Inventory is about 40% lower than it was this time last year. Our current inventory—which is the amount of time it would take to sell all the listings on the market—is about 1.9 months. This basically translates into a strong seller’s market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Sales are up and inventory is down compared to this time last year.%20localhost:4000/your-maplewoodsouth-orange-market-update.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Sales are up and inventory is down compared to this time last year.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to sell your home, then now is a great time to do it. If you’re looking to buy a home, there are still some really great homes out there for you. The key is to educate yourself about the market so when you find that home you love, you can act decisively about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, please contact me directly by phone or email. I’d be glad to help you with all your real estate needs!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/your-maplewoodsouth-orange-market-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/your-maplewoodsouth-orange-market-update.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to My New YouTube Page!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/X74K2jPZR7w&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to take a few minutes today to welcome you to my new YouTube channel. Some of the things you can expect from my videos are great sellers tips, buyer tips, listing videos, and real estate market updates. I really want this channel to be a great resource for all your real estate needs. If you’d like to know more about a specific topic, let me know and I’ll make a video about it. Until then, please feel free to look around and peruse. Have a great day!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-new-youtube-page.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-new-youtube-page.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
